Finding Aid for Renewal Ministries videotapes, 1974-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Renewal Ministries videotapes 1974-2009
Renewal Ministries.
2009079 Ba 2
27 linear feet
32 videotapes oversize
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection of videotapes was the gift of Renewal Ministries (donor no. 10145 ) and came to the library in 2008. Additional materials were received in 2012.
Further additions to the papers are possible.
The collection is open without restriction; no copies may be made except with the permission of the donor.
Renewal Ministries is an offshoot of the Word of God, an ecumenical charismatic Christian Community located in Ann Arbor, Michigan. Founded in 1980 by Ralph Martin as a lay Catholic organization, its purpose is to renew Catholic life and ministry, which it does through television, radio, conferences, and rallies, evangelization schools, books, tapes, and worldwide mission trips. As president of the organization, Ralph Martin has since 1982 hosted a weekly television program -- The Choices We Face.
The Renewal Ministries collection consists of videotapes (various formats) of organizational outreach programs, retreats, and rallies. The bulk of the collection is made up of videotapes of the long-running television program hosted by Ralph Martin entitled "The Choices we Face." There are other tapes of rallies held in Lithuania, Poland, and Jerusalem. Other materials predate the establishment of the organization. These include conferences held at Notre Dame and in Kansas City in the 1970s. The collection also includes some publications written by Martin, many of these in European languages.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Catholic Church--United States.; Catholics.; Choices we face.; Pentecostalism--Catholic Church.; Renewal Ministries (Organization)
Contributors:
Martin, Ralph, 1942-
Genre Terms:
Motion pictures.; Videotapes.
- Servant Ministries Annual Retreats
  - 1986, U-matic videotapes
    - The Holiness of God (Box 1)
    - Our Encounter with the Holiness of God (Box 1)
    - Growing in Holiness (Box 1)
    - Holiness and Suffering (Box 1)
  - 1988, 1 in. reel
    - Fear of the Lord 10/28/1988
      (also VHS videotape in Box 1)
    - The Passion, Part 1 10/29/1988
    - The Passion, Part 2 10/29/1988
    - Our Response to the Passion 10/29/1988
    - Mary's Example and Message, VHS videotape only (Box 1)
- Fire Rallies
  - Ann Shields, speaker, Providence, R.I. 4/5/1986, 1 in. reel
  - Ann Shields, speaker, Baltimore, MD 11/14/1987, 1 in. reel
  - Ann Shields, speaker, Orlando, Fl. 11/18/1989, 1 in. reel
  - Lithuania rallies 1993-1994
    - Fire in Lithuania, Ann Shields, speaker, 1 in. reel
    - Love and Forgiveness (Lithuania), Ralph Martin speaker, 1 in. reel
    - God Wants To Change You (Lithuania), Fr. Michael Scanlan speaker February 1993, 1 in. reel
    - "Fire in Lithuania" (compilation of speakers -- Shields, Martin, and Scanlan), U-matic videotape (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Lithuania videotapes, 4 videotapes Betacam (TM); 5 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 1)
  - "Fire in Jerusalem, U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - Nashville Fire Rally 1994, U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - "Faith" Ralph Martin speaker 1996 Rally (produced by Catholic Focus Productions), U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - Zidona Gora, Poland, Ralph Martin and Peter Herbeck speakers March 1993, 2 VHS videotape (Box 2)
- Conferences and Speaking Engagements, 1 in. reel
  - Crisis of Truth
    - The Attack on God's Word May 1982
    - Truth and Morality
    - The Uniqueness of Jesus
    - The Second Coming
    - The Coming Judgement
- MCA Talks, 1 in. reels unless otherwise indicated
  - Cultural Christianity and Salvation 10/18/1984
  - I Solemnly Assure You 11/15/1984
  - Is God For Us? 2/21/1985
  - Knowing God 3/21/1985
  - The Holy Spirit and the Gift of Life 4/18/1985
  - Love and Obedience 5/16/1985
  - Why Be a Christian 11/17/1985
  - The End of Time 12/19/1985
  - Friendship with God Through Personal Prayer 3/20/1986, U-matic videotape
  - Faith and Repentance 6/19/1986
  - A Life Pleasing to God 8/21/1986
  - Joy 9/19/1986
  - Daily Life with God 11/05/1987
  - Trusting God 6/18/1987
  - The Joy that is Set Before Us 5/12/1988
  - The Primordial Prayer 12/15/1988
  - The Promise of a Lasting City 2/17/1989
- Miscellaneous
  - 1974 Notre Dame Conference, "The Light of Christ", U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - 1977 Kansas City Conference, "Jesus is Lord", U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - Kollegger testimony; John and Evelyn Siler testimony, Betacam videotape (Box 2)
  - Servant Ministries excerpts 1990, VHS videotape (Box 2)
  - Servant Ministries November 1991, Betacam videotape (Box 2)
  - Mother Angelica and Russ Valvo Interview, U-matic videotape (Box 2)
  - The Choices We Face excerpts, 5 VHS videotapes (Box 3)
  - The Times We Live In, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 3)
- The Choices We Face, VHS videotapes; beginning in 2002, the series included VHS and/or Betacam tapes
  - 1982-1999
    - Untitled, 1 (Box 4)
    - Close up with Ralph Martin, 3 (Box 4)
    - Lies of Sexual Revolution, 4 (Box 4)
    - What is the Problem?, 5 (Box 4)
    - Is Jesus the Only Way?, 6 (Box 4)
    - The Times We Live In, 7 (Box 4)
    - Who is Jesus?, 8 (Box 4)
    - The Choices we Face, 9 (Box 4)
    - Close up with Ralph Martin, 10 (Box 4)
    - Faithful until the End, 11 (Box 4)
    - Return of the Lord, 12 (Box 4)
    - A Time of Visitation, 13 (Box 4)
    - Life is Short, 14 (Box 4)
    - Eternal Perspective, 15 (Box 4)
    - Healing and Death, 16 (Box 4)
    - Two Kingdoms, 17 (Box 4)
    - Cutting the Knot, 18 (Box 4)
    - Understanding the Church, 19 (Box 4)
    - Christianity is Real, 20 (Box 4)
    - Mercy and Judgment, 21 (Box 4)
    - Rise and Fall of Nation, 22 (Box 4)
    - Cultural Christianity, 23 (Box 4)
    - From Death to Life, 24 (Box 4)
    - Entering God's Kingdom, 25 (Box 4)
    - Entering God's Kingdom, 26 (Box 4)
    - A Crisis of Truth, 27 (Box 5)
    - Undermining God's Word, 28 (Box 5)
    - Knowing God's Word, 29 (Box 5)
    - Coming to Grips with Jesus, 30 (Box 5)
    - Jesus: All That Is Needed, 31 (Box 5)
    - God's Wisdom or Our Own, 32 (Box 5)
    - Is Ignorance Bliss?, 33 (Box 5)
    - The Second Coming, 34 (Box 5)
    - Signs of the Times, 35 (Box 5)
    - Reward and Vindication, 36 (Box 5)
    - Two Races of Men, 37 (Box 5)
    - Mother Angelica, Part I, 38 (Box 5)
    - Mother Angelica, Part II, 39 (Box 5)
    - Why Be a Christian?, 40 (Box 5)
    - Is God for Us?, 41 (Box 5)
    - Dead to Sin, Alive to God, 42 (Box 5)
    - Wall Street to Christ, 43 (Box 5)
    - On Christian Marriage, 44 (Box 5)
    - Made for Holiness, 45 (Box 5)
    - Fear of the Lord, 46 (Box 5)
    - Suffering and Holiness, 47 (Box 5)
    - Natural Disasters, 48 (Box 5)
    - Obedience and Love, 49 (Box 5)
    - Is Going to Church Enough?, 50 (Box 5)
    - True Peace and Security, 51 (Box 6)
    - Conversation With Fr. Michael Scanlan, 52 (Box 6)
    - Attributes of God, 53 (Box 6)
    - Called to be Holy, 54 (Box 6)
    - Encountering God's Holiness, 55 (Box 6)
    - God's Merciful Warnings, 56 (Box 6)
    - Ordering Our Priorities, 57 (Box 6)
    - Growing in Holiness, 58 (Box 6)
    - Conversation with Thomas S. Monaghan, 59 (Box 6)
    - Holiness and Suffering, 60 (Box 6)
    - Can God Forgive You?, 61 (Box 6)
    - How Should We Pray?, 62 (Box 6)
    - Through Eyes of Faith, 63 (Box 6)
    - Untitled, 65 (Box 6)
    - Holiness in Daily Life, 66 (Box 6)
    - A Life Pleasing to God, 67 (Box 6)
    - 10 Weeks to Better Marriage, 68 (Box 6)
    - The Facts About Your Feelings, 69 (Box 6)
    - Joy, 70 (Box 6)
    - Faith and Repentance, 71 (Box 6)
    - Close to God in Prayer, 72 (Box 6)
    - Christian Freedom, 73 (Box 6)
    - Mother Angelica III, 74 (Box 6)
    - Mother Angelica IV, 75 (Box 6)
    - What Jesus Wants, 76 (Box 6)
    - The End of Time, 77 (Box 6)
    - The Great Commission, 78 (Box 6)
    - Holding Fast/Pagan Culture, 79 (Box 6)
    - Only God Can Fill You, 80 (Box 6)
    - Mary, Prophetic Messenger, 81 (Box 6)
    - The Pearl of Great Price, 82 (Box 7)
    - Understanding Sickness and Sin, 83 (Box 7)
    - Will Many Be Saved?, 84 (Box 7)
    - Sex and Christian Freedom, 85 (Box 7)
    - Money and Christian Freedom I, 86 (Box 7)
    - Money and Christian Freedom II, 87 (Box 7)
    - Power and Christian Freedom, 88 (Box 7)
    - Woe, Those Who Lead Astray, 89 (Box 7)
    - Trusting God, 90 (Box 7)
    - Women Loved by God, 91 (Box 7)
    - Good News for Today's Women, 92 (Box 7)
    - Women-A Light to the World, 93 (Box 7)
    - Life with God, 94 (Box 7)
    - Waiting for the Lord, 95 (Box 7)
    - Pray Constantly, 96 (Box 7)
    - Family Life I, 97 (Box 7)
    - Family Life II, 98 (Box 7)
    - Daily Life with God, 99 (Box 7)
    - Greatness in Jesus, 100 (Box 7)
    - Make the Difference, 101 (Box 7)
    - Rock and Rebellion, 102 (Box 7)
    - Life in Heaven, 103 (Box 7)
    - The Joy of Heaven, 104 (Box 7)
    - What's the Real Issue, 105 (Box 7)
    - Mary's Example and Message, 107 (Box 7)
    - God Save Me!, 109 (Box 7)
    - Fear of the Lord, 110 (Box 7)
    - Family Life at the Martins, 112 (Box 7)
    - Christian Sexuality, 113 (Box 7)
    - The New Age Phenomena, 115 (Box 7)
    - The Promise of a Lasting City, 116 (Box 8)
    - Peace or Troubles in the World?, 117 (Box 8)
    - Why Fear God, 118 (Box 8)
    - Abortion, 119 (Box 8)
    - Pearl of Great Price, 120 (Box 8)
    - The Promises of God, 121 (Box 8)
    - Temptation and Agony in the Garden, 122 (Box 8)
    - The Promise of Gethsemane, 123 (Box 8)
    - Why Have You Forsaken Me?, 124 (Box 8)
    - Pilate and the Messiah, 125 (Box 8)
    - Legatus, 126 (Box 8)
    - What Happens to Kids at School?, 128 (Box 8)
    - Keeping Faith in College, 129 (Box 8)
    - Abortion II, 130 (Box 8)
    - Christmas Program: The Incarnation, 131 (Box 8)
    - The Cancer of Discontent, 147 (Box 8)
    - Call to Discipleship, 149 (Box 8)
    - Evangelizing the New Age, 151 (Box 8)
    - Humility, 153 (Box 8)
    - Patience, 154 (Box 8)
    - Why Do Kids Leave Church?, 155 (Box 8)
    - Modern Idolatry, 161 (Box 8)
    - Illusions of Power, 162 (Box 8)
    - Pruning and Patience, 163 (Box 8)
    - Holiness of Life, 164 (Box 8)
    - Nothing is Impossible with God, 165 (Box 8)
    - Abraham, 166 (Box 8)
    - Satan's Plan for You, 167 (Box 8)
    - A Shadow on our Face, 168 (Box 8)
    - Where Can I Turn for Help?, 169 (Box 9)
    - Saul and David, 171 (Box 9)
    - The Lord is Rescuing the Young, 172 (Box 9)
    - The Cross and Young Adults, 173 (Box 9)
    - Repentance, 174 (Box 9)
    - Witnessing in Our Times, 175 (Box 9)
    - Renewing the Work of Renewal, 176 (Box 9)
    - The Time of Our Visitation, 177 (Box 9)
    - Life Worthy of Living, 178 (Box 9)
    - Searching for Love, 179 (Box 9)
    - True Security, 180 (Box 9)
    - What Time is It? Looking Back Over 10 Years, 181 (Box 9)
    - The State of the Renewal, 182 (Box 9)
    - Real God for Real People, 183 (Box 9)
    - Moses: God Will Do It Anyway, 184 (Box 9)
    - The Trouble is in Your Head, 185 (Box 9)
    - Grace From God, 186 (Box 9)
    - Christmas Special (Box 9)
      (no number)
    - Seek First My Kingdom, 187 (Box 9)
    - Obedience, 188 (Box 9)
    - Breaking Pride, 189 (Box 9)
    - What's On Our Heart?, 190 (Box 9)
    - Our Heavenly Home, 191 (Box 9)
    - Faith, 193 (Box 9)
    - Bishop Sam Jacobs, 194 (Box 9)
    - Holiness and Evangelism, 195 (Box 9)
    - Living By Faith, 196 (Box 9)
    - The Great Physician, 197 (Box 9)
    - Hope in Christ, II, 198 (Box 9)
    - This Extraordinary Century, 199 (Box 9)
    - The Abortion Battle, 200 (Box 9)
    - Occupational Hazards, 201 (Box 9)
    - As the Father Has Loved, 202 (Box 9)
    - Parish Revival Renewal of Priests, 203 (Box 9)
    - Vatican View of the CCR, 204 (Box 9)
    - What is Baptism in Holy Spirit, 205 (Box 10)
    - The Duquesne Experience, 206 (Box 10)
    - The New Law of Love, 207 (Box 10)
    - Taking Up the Call, 208 (Box 10)
    - Pentecostal View of The Roman Catholic Church, 209 (Box 10)
    - Wounds That Heal, 210 (Box 10)
    - Catholics and the New Age, 211 (Box 10)
    - Christmas Special (Box 10)
    - The Only Title Worth Having, 212 (Box 10)
    - Commitment: In Good Time and In Bad, 213 (Box 10)
    - Heaven, 214 (Box 10)
    - Love and Forgiveness, 216 (Box 10)
    - The Duty to Evangelize, 217 (Box 10)
    - Call to Lithuania, 218 (Box 10)
    - Named in the Will, 219 (Box 10)
    - What Do Catholics Believe, 220 (Box 10)
    - The Church Universal, 221 (Box 10)
    - The Grand Banks Tragedy, 222 (Box 10)
    - Courage, 223 (Box 10)
    - A Birth Unto Hope, 224 (Box 10)
    - Bishop Sam Jacobs, 225 (Box 10)
    - Univ. Catholic Catechism, 226 (Box 10)
    - Signs of Our Times, 227 (Box 10)
    - A Catholic Springtime, 228 (Box 10)
    - Canadian Catholic Church, 229 (Box 10)
    - You Ready To Go Home?, 230 (Box 10)
    - How Should I Die?, 231 (Box 10)
    - Save the Innocents, 232 (Box 10)
    - Under the Circumstances, 233 (Box 10)
    - Evangelize or Secularize, 234 (Box 10)
    - 25 Years of Marriage, 235 (Box 10)
    - Hope, 236 (Box 10)
    - Living the New Covenant, 237 (Box 10)
    - God Wants to Change You, 238 (Box 10)
    - Fruit of the Vine, 239 (Box 10)
    - Fellowship in Holy Spirit, 240 (Box 11)
    - Blood of the Martyrs, 241 (Box 11)
    - Civilizations at War, 242 (Box 11)
    - Falling in Love with God, 243 (Box 11)
    - Sharing Your Faith, 244 (Box 11)
    - Hill of Crosses, 245 (Box 11)
    - What Is the Gospel?, 246 (Box 11)
    - Coming Home, 247 (Box 11)
    - Do It, Darn It, Do It?, 248 (Box 11)
    - Christian Freedom, 249 (Box 11)
    - A Call to Lithuania, 250 (Box 11)
    - Unconditional Love, 251 (Box 11)
    - The Next Teen Revolution, 252 (Box 11)
    - Urgency of the Task, 253 (Box 11)
    - Bishop MacDonald-Talk #1, 254 (Box 11)
    - The Spirit in Lithuania, 255 (Box 11)
    - Growth in Church of Jos, 256 (Box 11)
    - Veritatis Splendor, 257 (Box 11)
    - The Bread of Life, 258 (Box 11)
    - Youth Chastity, 259 (Box 11)
    - God's Work in The World, 260 (Box 11)
    - Saved by Grace/Faith, 263 (Box 11)
    - Lift Up Christ, 264 (Box 11)
    - Ann Shield's Talk, 265 (Box 11)
    - Bishop MacDonald-Talk #2, 266 (Box 11)
    - A Healing Story, 267 (Box 11)
    - Overcome Evil With God, 268 (Box 11)
    - Easter 1994 (Box 11)
    - As Mill Draws Near, 269 (Box 12)
    - What Spirit Saying, 270 (Box 12)
    - New Power/New Time, 271 (Box 12)
    - Fr. Ed Fride, 272 (Box 12)
    - Eastern Europe, 273 (Box 12)
    - Full of Grace, 274 (Box 12)
    - Great Love, 275 (Box 12)
    - On Women, 276 (Box 12)
    - Repentance, 278 (Box 12)
    - Five Year Advent, 279 (Box 12)
    - A Parish Prepares, I, 280 (Box 12)
    - A Parish Prepares, II, 281 (Box 12)
    - Debbie Herbeck, 282 (Box 12)
    - Saints/Martyrs, 283 (Box 12)
    - Eternal Perspective, 284 (Box 12)
    - Mike Murphy, 285 (Box 12)
    - A Servant Leader, 286 (Box 12)
    - Eastern Europe, II, 287 (Box 12)
    - Universal Jubilee, 288 (Box 12)
    - Joy!, 289 (Box 12)
    - Courage, 290 (Box 12)
    - Lito Urgino, 291 (Box 12)
    - The Deaconate, 292 (Box 12)
    - Freedom from Fear, 293 (Box 12)
    - Bishop Sam Jacobs Studio Talk, 294 (Box 12)
    - Toronto Rally -- RCM, 295 (Box 12)
    - Medjugorje -- Part I, 296 (Box 12)
    - Toronto Rally -- Bedard, 297 (Box 12)
    - Ottawa -- PJH, 298 (Box 12)
    - Kieda Testimony, 299 (Box 12)
    - RCM Studio, 300 (Box 12)
    - JPII Conf. -- Dulles, 301 (Box 12)
    - AES Studio, 302 (Box 12)
    - Medjugorje, 303 (Box 12)
    - Allentown Rally, 304 (Box 12)
    - DeBisschop Test, 305 (Box 12)
    - Easter (Box 13)
    - Christmas (Box 13)
    - Pentecost (Box 13)
    - Toronto Ralley-AES, 306 (Box 13)
    - Eastern Europe I, 307 (Box 13)
    - Rea Testimony, 308 (Box 13)
    - JPII Conf. -- Forrest, 309 (Box 13)
    - Holder Testimony, 310 (Box 13)
    - MacDonald Studio, 311 (Box 13)
    - Bartolovich Testimony, 312 (Box 13)
    - Len DeVenere, 313 (Box 13)
    - JPII Conf. -- RCM, 314 (Box 13)
    - Irvine Testimony, 315 (Box 13)
    - Ottawa Rally -- RCM, 316 (Box 13)
    - BP. F.M. -- Studio, 317 (Box 13)
    - Ottawa Rally-AES, 318 (Box 13)
    - Medujugorje -- Part III, 319 (Box 13)
    - The Grace of the Jubilee, 320 (Box 13)
    - The Significance of Baptism, 321 (Box 13)
    - Hungarian, 322 (Box 13)
    - Being Humbled and Purified, 323 (Box 13)
    - Father John Rea, 324 (Box 13)
    - Let My People Go, 325 (Box 13)
    - Marilyn Geyer, 326 (Box 13)
    - The Acts of the Apostles Continues, 327 (Box 13)
    - Judy Polista, 328 (Box 13)
    - Waiting for the Fulfillment of God's Promises, 329 (Box 13)
    - Rob and Mary Carpenter, 331 (Box 13)
    - Hope, 332 (Box 13)
    - Confirmation, 333 (Box 13)
    - The Prayer of the Holy Spirit, 334 (Box 13)
    - Dialogue with Two Bishops, 335 (Box 13)
    - Katalin Graszli, 336 (Box 13)
    - Celibacy, 337 (Box 13)
    - John and Evelyn Siler, 338 (Box 13)
    - The Love of Jesus at Work in Us, 339 (Box 13)
    - Erwin and Carolyn Kollegger, 340 (Box 14)
    - Mary's Role in Our Time, 341 (Box 14)
    - Carmine and Pat Ferragamo, 342 (Box 14)
    - Growing in Virtue, 343 (Box 14)
    - Zsuzanna Nagy, 344 (Box 14)
    - JM God's Providential Care, 345 (Box 14)
    - Christmas (Box 14)
    - Pentecost (Box 14)
    - New Springtime in Lithuania, 347 (Box 14)
    - Mary's Prophetic Warning, 348 (Box 14)
    - New Springtime in Ghana, 349 (Box 14)
    - You Have An Anointing, 350 (Box 14)
    - Therese of Lisieux I, 351 (Box 14)
    - The Father, 352 (Box 14)
    - Love, 353 (Box 14)
    - Reconciliation, 354 (Box 14)
    - Jim Murphy, 355 (Box 14)
    - Jesus and Hope, 356 (Box 14)
    - Archbishop Tamkevecius, 357 (Box 14)
    - Called to Mission, 358 (Box 14)
    - Therese of Lisieux II, 359 (Box 14)
    - The Acts of the Apostles and Us, 360 (Box 14)
    - Janet I, 361 (Box 14)
    - St. Bonaventure, 362 (Box 14)
    - The Rise and Fall of the Churches, 363 (Box 14)
    - Tony and Pauline Ruta Test, 364 (Box 14)
    - Mike Ruta Testimony, 365 (Box 14)
    - What is the Spirit Saying?, 366 (Box 14)
    - Jubilee: The Season of Release, 367 (Box 14)
    - Janet II, 368 (Box 14)
    - Mission and Daily Life, 370 (Box 14)
    - Invade My Privacy, 371 (Box 14)
    - Savior of Marriages, 372 (Box 14)
    - Christmas 1999 (Box 14)
  - 2000
    - Forgiveness, 0001 (Box 14)
    - Sister Emmanuel-A Report on Medjugorje, 0002 (Box 14)
    - Jubilee, 0003 (Box 14)
    - A Prophetic Sense, 0004 (Box 15)
    - Holiness and Conversion, 0005 (Box 15)
    - Babsie Preaching in Toronto, 0006 (Box 15)
    - Mission I, 0007 (Box 15)
    - Youth, 0008 (Box 15)
    - The Power of the Holy Spirit, 0009 (Box 15)
    - St. Maximilian Kolbe, 0010 (Box 15)
    - Practical Faith Sharing, 0011 (Box 15)
    - Ralph Preaching in Toronto, 0012 (Box 15)
    - An Understanding of End Times I, 0013 (Box 15)
    - Bob and Jan...one year later, 0014 (Box 15)
    - Mary, 0015 (Box 15)
    - Evangelization, 0016 (Box 15)
    - Lives Touched in Medjugorje, 0017 (Box 15)
    - A Parish in Renewal w/Fr. Graham Keep, 0018 (Box 15)
    - A Look at the Church, w Archbishop C. Chaput, 0019 (Box 15)
    - Peter Preaching in Ontario, 0020 (Box 15)
    - Mary -- Star of Evangelization, 0021 (Box 15)
    - Mission II, 0022 (Box 15)
    - Healing, 0023 (Box 15)
    - Challenges for the Church, with Bishop Sam Jacobs, 0024 (Box 15)
    - Bob and Loretta Bray Testimony, 0025 (Box 15)
    - Easter 2000, 0026 (Box 15)
  - 2001
    - From Jerusalem to Rome, 0101 (Box 15)
    - Understanding Mary, 0102 (Box 15)
    - Jesus is Lord, 0103 (Box 15)
    - Catherine of Sienna I, 0104 (Box 15)
    - Catherine of Sienna II, 0105 (Box 15)
    - A Story of Faith, 0106 (Box 15)
    - The Church in Africa, 0107 (Box 15)
    - Faith Works!, 0108 (Box 15)
    - Jesus Saves Families, 0109 (Box 15)
    - A Cross Called Cancer, 0110 (Box 15)
    - Teresa of Avila I, 0111 (Box 15)
    - Teresa of Avila II, 0112 (Box 15)
    - Teresa of Avila III, 0113 (Box 16)
    - A Family Regathered, 0114 (Box 16)
    - The Church Today, 0115 (Box 16)
    - Healing in the Church Today, 0116 (Box 16)
    - Jesus is Alive, 0117 (Box 16)
    - They Call Me Father, 0118 (Box 16)
    - The Mission Unfolds, 0119 (Box 16)
    - A Tragedy Remembered, 0120 (Box 16)
    - Catholic and Jews, 0121 (Box 16)
    - Gods Plan for Israel, 0122 (Box 16)
    - Questions for Ralph, 0123 (Box 16)
    - Life with Jesus, 0124 (Box 16)
    - Evangelization, 0125 (Box 16)
    - The Call to Holiness, 0126 (Box 16)
    - Growing in Holiness, 0127 (Box 16)
    - Hope in the Pain, 0128 (Box 16)
    - Saints and Martyrs, 0129 (Box 16)
    - St. Francis de Sales, 0130 (Box 16)
    - Elements of the Gospel, 0131 (Box 16)
    - A Search of Faith, 0132 (Box 16)
  - 2002, VHS tapes
    - Life Issues, 0201 (Box 16)
    - Wash Up and Come, 0202 (Box 16)
    - Saints I, 0203 (Box 16)
    - Joy of the Lord, 0204 (Box 16)
    - Live Audience Question and Answer I, 0205 (Box 16)
    - Worrier or Warrior?, 0206 (Box 16)
    - Student Life, 0207 (Box 16)
    - St. Catherine's Heaven/Hell, 0208 (Box 16)
    - Abortion, 0209 (Box 16)
    - Never A Bad Day, 0210 (Box 16)
    - Ministry to Women, 0211 (Box 16)
    - Peace and Justice, 0212 (Box 16)
    - Seeking The Face of Jesus, 0213 (Box 16)
    - Spiritual Phenomena, 0214 (Box 16)
    - Saints II, 0215 (Box 16)
    - Father and Son Conversion I, 0216 (Box 17)
    - Father and Son Conversion II, 0217 (Box 17)
    - Journey to Freedom, 0218 (Box 17)
    - Africa, 0219 (Box 17)
    - John of Cross World View, 0220 (Box 17)
    - Live Audience Question and Answer II, 0221 (Box 17)
    - Healing Document, 0222 (Box 17)
    - Brother Suffering, 0223 (Box 17)
    - Campus Crusade, 0224 (Box 17)
    - Intercessory Prayer, 0225 (Box 17)
    - Light in the Darkness, 0226 (Box 17)
    - New Age to New Life, 0229 (Box 17)
    - The Humility of God, 0230 (Box 17)
    - Forgiveness for the Weak or for the Strong?, 0231 (Box 17)
    - Fatima, 0232 (Box 17)
    - End Times, 0233 (Box 17)
  - 2002, 0201-0233; BetacamSP 30 and BetacamSP 60 (Box 20)
    (missing some program numbers)
  - 2003, VHS tapes
    - Rosary, 0301 (Box 17)
    - The Courage to be Catholic, 0302 (Box 17)
    - Go to Joseph, 0303 (Box 17)
    - 2nd Coming and Final Judgment, 0304 (Box 17)
    - Christ -- Heart of the Church, 0305 (Box 17)
    - Francis DeSales, 0306 (Box 17)
    - Fragrance Filled the Room, 0307 (Box 17)
    - Outreach and Missions, 0308 (Box 17)
    - Live Audience '03, 0309 (Box 17)
    - Our Lady of Guadalupe, 0310 (Box 17)
    - A Woman's Story, 0311 (Box 17)
    - Search for Truth, 0312 (Box 17)
    - Legacy of John Paul II, 0313 (Box 17)
    - The Mercy of God, 0314 (Box 17)
    - Holy Spirit and the Church, 0315 (Box 17)
    - Are You Desperate for God?, 0316 (Box 17)
    - Healing Power of the Eucharist, 0317 (Box 17)
    - Married Missionaries, 0318 (Box 17)
    - Generosity to God, 0319 (Box 17)
    - Loaves and Fishes, 0320 (Box 18)
    - Born Into New Life, 0321 (Box 18)
    - Doubletalk, 0322 (Box 18)
    - Take Delight in the Lord, 0323 (Box 18)
    - Fighting Spiritual Warfare, 0324 (Box 18)
    - My 5 Best Decisions, 0325 (Box 18)
    - Charles deFoucauld, 0326 (Box 18)
    - Satan's E-mail, 0327 (Box 18)
    - Reform-What will it Require, 0328 (Box 18)
    - To Call to Hope, 0329 (Box 18)
    - State of the Church, 0330 (Box 18)
    - New Springtime in Lithuania, 0347 (Box 18)
  - 2004, VHS tapes
    - The Fire of God's Love, 0401 (Box 18)
    - He Gave Himself for Me, 0402 (Box 18)
    - The Power of Prayer, 0403 (Box 18)
    - The Passion, 0404 (Box 18)
    - Let Go!, 0405 (Box 18)
    - Mission Program, 0406 (Box 18)
    - The Little Flower, 0407 (Box 18)